Good. Praise God in Jesus name. Let's
give him another round of applause.
Amen.
We're going to uh start off with reading
the law. We're going to turn to Exodus
20. At all Israel of God locations, we
always start off with reading the law.
law is simple. It's from God. And it's
the L. And if you keep it, then you put
yourself in position
to be in the running for eternal life.
Amen.
>> Got to read them every week cuz seem
like sometimes we can't get it right.
>> Exodus chapter 20 and we're going to
start reading at verse one.
Exodus chapter 20,
we're going to start reading at verse
one.
Like everybody said, go ahead and start
reading, bro.
>> And God spake all these words, saying,
>> I am the Lord thy God, which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt,
out of the house of bondage.
>> Right?
>> Thou shalt have no other gods before me.
>> Thou shalt not make unto thee any graven
image, or any likeness of anything that
is in heaven above, or that is in the
earth beneath,
>> or that is in the water under the earth.
>> Right?
>> Thou shalt not bow down thyself to them,
nor serve them. For I, the Lord thy God,
am a jealous God, visiting iniquity of
the fathers, upon the children, unto the
third and four generations of them that
hate me,
>> and showing mercy unto thousands of them
that love me, and keep my commandments.
>> Yeah.
>> Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain. For the Lord will not
hold him guiltless that taketh his name
in vain.
>> Right?
>> Remember the Sabbath day to keep it
holy.
Six days shalt thou labor and do all thy
work, but the seventh day it is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God. In it thou
shalt not do any work. Thou nor thy son,
nor thy daughter, thy man's servant, nor
thy maid servant, nor thy cattle, nor
thy stranger that within thy gate. For
in six days the Lord made heaven and
earth, the sea, and all that in them is,
and rested the seventh day.
>> Wherefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath
day, and hallowed it.
>> Amen. Honor thy father and thy mother,
that thy days may be long upon the land
which the Lord thy God giveth thee.
>> Yeah.
>> Thou shalt not kill. Thou shalt not
commit adultery. Thou shalt not steal.
>> Thou shall not be a false witness
against thy neighbor.
>> Thou shalt not cover thy neighbor's
house. Thou shalt not coveret thy
neighbor's wife, nor his manservant, nor
his maid servant, nor his ax, nor his
ass, nor anything that is thy neighbor.
>> Amen. Let's turn to Ecclesiastes chapter
12.
All throughout the Bible, the Lord is
reminding us just keep his commandments
and we should be good if we do that.
Ecclesiastes chapter 12,
we're going to read verses 13 and 14.
Ecclesiastes chapter 12.
We're going to read verses 13 and 14.
You get it? Go ahead.
>> Let us hear the conclusion of the whole
matter.
>> Uhhuh. Fear God and keep his
commandments. For this is the whole duty
of man.
>> For God shall bring every work into
judgment
>> with every secret thing, whether it be
good or whe it be evil.
>> Amen. Let's go to Revelation 22, last
chapter, last page in some Bibles. We're
almost at the very end. Let's see if
anything change. Revelation chapter 22.
We're going to read two verses here.
Verses 14 and 15. Revelation 22,
we going to read verses 14 and 15. You
get it? Go ahead and start reading.
>> Blessed are they that do his
commandments
>> that they may have right to the tree of
life,
>> right?
>> And may enter into the gates into the
city.
>> Go ahead.
>> For without are dogs and sorcerers and
whoreongers and murderers and idoltors
and whosoever love it and make it a
light.
>> Praise God for the reading of the law in
Jesus name.
Amen. At this moment, we're going to
have our uh children. You all can
dismiss to children's class. Give them a
second to
head along their merry way.
Amen.
I wish I was taught this as a child.
had to go through all them lies first,
>> right?
>> Amen.
>> All right. Praise God in Jesus name.
Welcome back to the Israel of God
Orlando. My name is Brother Maris. I
will be your teacher for today. And
reading for me today is Brother Donnie.
And uh at the Israel of God, we teach by
subject and title. We can't read the
whole Bible to you in one day. Um, so we
try to break it down by subject and
title and hopefully by the subject and
titles over time we'll get a very good
understanding of what this book is
trying to get us to understand. Amen.
>> So today's title is
the Lord's day is the last day. Amen.
>> And uh I feel like the Lord caused me to
put this lesson together because you
know I I speak for myself first. When I
was growing up I was always taught that
the Lord's day was Sunday, right? And
even now when I hear people say that,
I'm like, man, you know, I kind of
cringe a little bit because uh the
Lord's day is not tied to a day of the
week, right? Like most people uh believe
in this world. So what we going to try
to do today is we going to try to get a
very good understanding of what the
Bible says that the Lord's day is. And
we going to see if it's Sunday.
>> Yeah.
>> Or we going to see if it's this day when
the Lord returns. Amen.
>> Amen.
>> Let's go to Revelation. We're going to
start this out in Revelation because
this is where we get it from. So, might
as well go to the source. Let's go to
Revelation chapter 1.
And we going to see if we find
Sunday in here anywhere.
Revelation chapter one.
And it's amaz, you know, you look back
on some of the things that you once
believed. It's amazing sometimes you
believe these things, right? It shows
that we uh well, like I said, I speak
for myself. I wasn't really uh there to
learn these words yet. I was there to
Somebody speak to me.
>> Right. Revelation chapter one and we
going to read one verse here. Verse 10.
When you get it, go ahead and start
reading.
>> I was in the spirit on the Lord's day.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And heard behind me a great voice as of
a trumpet.
>> Now, did this say Sunday?
>> No,
>> it did not. Right. So, they have taken I
always say they have hijacked the word
of God, these Gentiles. And the thing
is, why is it so important that the
Gentiles have hijacked the word of God?
Is because the Gentiles have colonized
almost the majority of the world. So
what they did was they colonized and
they indoctrinated you.
>> So if you was colonized by the Gentiles
in some form or fashion, then you got
this understanding that this that Sunday
was the Lord's day. But that's not what
it says. And so what we going to do is
we're going to uh get a good
understanding of what the Bible says the
Lord's day is. Um we're going to start
this out by turning to 2 Samuel uh the
seventh chapter. And the reason we come
here is the first thing we got to show
is that the Lord is going to come. And
when the Lord comes, this is the Lord's
day. This is that day that he's
referring to, not necessarily a day of
the week. And so, we going to see why he
even has to come in the first place.
Second Samuel,
we going to turn to chapter 7.
2 Samuel chapter 7 and we going to start
reading at verse 12.
2 Samuel chapter 7
verse 12. Now, this is uh a prophecy to
David. Um, but we gonna see if this is
actually talking about Solomon, right?
Because we know Solomon became king over
Israel for 40 years, right?
>> But this ain't talking about Solomon,
>> right? When you get it, go and start
reading at verse 12. Go ahead.
>> And when thy days be fulfilled,
>> and thou shalt sleep with thy fathers.
>> So, so David is going to die. Go ahead.
>> I will set up thy seed after thee,
>> which shall proceed out of thy bowels,
>> and I will establish his kingdom. Now,
we know that we read this book, you
know, pretty clear. Solomon, his son,
his seed, became king, right? But keep
reading, though.
>> 13.
>> Uhhuh.
>> He shall build an house for my name, and
I will establish the throne of his
kingdom forever.
>> Wait a minute. So, we did see Solomon
build a kingdom, right? And built he he
built he built a a house for my name,
but his kingdom wasn't established
forever. Solomon's laying with his
fathers in the dirt, right?
>> Okay, keep reading. 14. I will be th I
will be his father.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And he shall be my son.
>> Yeah.
>> If he commit iniquity, I will test him
with the rod of men.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And with the stripes of the children of
men.
>> Keep reading.
>> But my mercy shall not depart away from
him.
>> Uhhuh.
>> As I took it from Saul,
>> whom I put away before thee.
>> Read.
>> And thine house and thy kingdom shall be
established forever
>> before thee.
>> Thy throne shall be established forever.
>> So this throne shall be established
forever. Right? Let's go to Luke chapter
1 because we need to understand who is
actually going to sit on this throne.
Luke chapter 1.
We just trying to set the foundation
here because the Lord is going to come
and that time when he comes, that is his
day.
Luke chapter 1,
we're going to start reading at verse
30.
Luke chapter 1,
we're going to start reading at verse
30.
Go ahead.
>> And the angel said unto her,
>> "Fear not, Mary, for thou hast found
favor with God."
>> "And behold, thou shall conceive in thy
womb, and bring forth a son, and shall
call his name Jesus."
>> So, we talking about Jesus. Go ahead.
32.
>> He shall be great,
>> and shall be called the son of the
highest,
>> right?
>> And the Lord shall give unto him the
throne of his father David. Now, we
didn't see Jesus sit on the throne when
he came the first time,
>> right? He shall he was called the son of
the highest because when he was on
walking on earth, he was called son of
man. Right.
>> But we didn't see him take the seat on
David's throne. Read 33.
>> And he shall reign over the house of
Jacob forever.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And of his kingdom, there shall be no
end.
>> So if there's no going to be no end, if
this already happened, then he will
still be king right now. Right?
>> But he's not king right now.
>> Right?
>> So this is a future prophecy. Go to
Zechariah the 14th chapter.
We just trying to establish that the
Lord has to become king and how he's
going to do it.
Zechariah the 14th chapter. So the Lord
told uh actually that was in second
Samuel that was uh Nathan the prophet.
He was telling you know uh David that
your the seed of your uh the seed of
your uh body is going to be set on the
throne forever. And we came here, we see
that the angel now has come and he's
telling them, look, Jesus is going to
sit on the throne of David forever.
Zechariah, Zechariah the 14th chapter,
we're going to read one verse here. Just
this constant theme, he has to come back
to take over this throne. Zechariah 14,
we're going to start reading at verse 9.
When you get it, go ahead and start
reading.
>> And the Lord shall be king over all the
earth.
>> In that day shall there be one Lord and
his name one. So this is prophesying
that the Lord whom we just read about
was Jesus. We got him by name in Luke
chapter 1. He is going to be king over
all the earth. Go to Daniel chapter 7
and we going to walk this thing down.
Daniel chapter 7
and we going to start reading at verse
13. All this is showing that there is a
coming king and when this king come his
kingdom going to be established forever.
Right? This is very very simple and
basic stuff.
You got these people out here saying
that uh well he didn't sit on David's
throne so he wasn't the one. He just
ain't do it yet. He's coming back and he
is going to do that. And that's what
your faith should be in that he's going
to come back and set up that throne.
Daniel chapter 7,
we gonna start reading at verse 13.
Daniel chapter 7 verse 13. When you get
it, go ahead and start reading.
>> I saw in a night vision,
>> and behold, one like the son of man came
with the clouds of heaven
>> and came to the ancients of days, and
they brought him near before him.
>> Go ahead.
>> And there was given him dominion
>> and glory, and the kingdom that all
people, nations, and languages should
serve him.
>> Right? His dominion is an everlasting
dominion which shall not pass away and
his kingdom that which shall not be
destroyed.
>> Amen. So again, there's one that's
coming when we saw his name was Jesus.
He's going to come and he's going to set
up his kingdom. But there's something
that people are missing about this.
Let's go to Psalm 110
because right now who ruled the earth?
Gentiles, men do, flesh do, right?
All right.
So, we going to see
that if the Lord got to come take this
thing over, are they going to just hand
it to him? No, they not. They are not.
Psalm 110.
And we're going to start reading at
verse one.
Psalm 110.
We're going to start reading at verse
one. When you get it, go ahead.
>> The Lord said unto my Lord,
>> Uhhuh.
>> sit thou at my right hand until I make
thy enemies thy foottool.
>> So David said, the Lord said unto my
Lord, his Lord is Jesus. And his Lord is
the father, right? That's the only one
that's sitting at the right hand. Go
ahead. Verse two.
>> The Lord shall send the rod of thy
strength out of Zion.
>> Rule thou in the midst of thine enemies.
>> Yeah. Go ahead.
>> Thy people shall be willing in that day.
>> Hold on. Oh, I'm sorry. Skip down to
five.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> The Lord at thy right hand shall strike
through kings in the days of his wrath.
>> In the day of his wrath. Yeah. Because
we focusing on the Lord's day. He said
he going to strike through kings. He got
to strike through kings. If he's
supposed to be the king and his king's
already here, then how he going to take
over that kingship?
>> Right. Read verse six.
>> He shall judge among the heen.
>> Uhhuh.
>> He shall fill the places with dead
bodies.
>> Oh, that's sweet Jesus.
>> Go ahead.
>> He shall wound the heads over many
countries.
>> So we see that there's going to be a
kingdom established. And when this
kingdom is established, Jesus going to
sit on the throne of David. And once he
does that, it's not going to end.
>> But it's a nice transition here that's
telling you, look, he going to have to
go through some people.
>> Right now, what we going to look at is
since he got to go through some people,
we going to see, is he coming by itself,
right? Let's go to First Thessalonians
chapter 4.
because he could just send an angel down
and just
>> breathe on them and they dead.
>> But that's not the plan that he has
outlined in this book.
>> First Thessalonians 4. And we believe
this book, right?
>> Amen.
I can only teach you what's written
here, so we might as well investigate
it.
1 Thessalonians chapter 4.
So he got to strike through kings to get
to his kingship. He got to fill the
places with dead bodies. We just trying
to see if he going to be by himself.
First Thessalonians chapter 4, we going
to start reading at verse 15. 1
Thessalonians 4 verse1 15. When you get
it, go ahead.
>> For this we say unto you by the word of
the Lord.
>> That we which are alive and remain unto
the coming of the Lord shall not prevent
them which are sleep.
>> So he's talking about, you know, uh he's
not going to prevent them which are
dead. Go ahead. Verse 16. For the Lord
himself shall descend from heaven
>> with a shout, with the voice of an
archangel,
>> and with the trumpet of God,
>> and the dead in Christ shall rise first.
>> So, he's coming down from the third
heaven, cuz that's where he's at,
>> right? And uh read verse 17. Go ahead.
>> Then we which are alive and remain shall
be caught up together with them in the
clouds to meet the Lord in the air, and
so shall we ever be with the Lord.
>> So, he said they going to meet him in
the clouds. The clouds is the second
heaven. So he coming down from heaven.
They coming up. The dead going to rise
and then everybody else going to rise up
and they going to beat him in the
clouds. Right. But he said we Paul
talking in the flesh.
>> Yeah.
>> He talking to men,
>> right? Let's go to uh Zechariah the 14th
chapter.
>> Let's take a look at these men because
last time I checked, men don't fly,
right? How you going to meet somebody in
the clouds?
Zechariah the 14th chapter. We're going
to read two verses here.
We just trying to establish this this
day of the Lord.
See if we can make sense of it.
Zechariah the 14th chapter,
we're going to start reading at verse
one.
When you get it, go ahead.
>> Behold, the day of the Lord cometh.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And thy spoil shall be divided in the
midst of
>> Now pay attention.
>> midst of thee.
>> Yeah. shall be divided and messed. Now,
pay attention to how many places we
going to read day of the Lord because
this what we going to read is this is
the Lord's day when these things happen.
>> Right?
>> Skip down to verse uh five and continue
because we we trying to investigate
right now. It said that the Lord going
to fill the places with dead bodies.
>> And I'm just trying to figure out if
he's coming by himself. Skip down to
verse five and continue. Go ahead.
>> And ye shall flee to the valley of the
mountains.
>> For the valley of the mountains shall
reach unto Isa.
>> Yeah. Ye shall flee like as he fled from
before the earthquake in the days of
Uzziah, king of Judah.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And the Lord my God shall come and all
his saints with thee.
>> So he's coming and he got the saints
coming with him.
>> Where'd he get these saints from?
>> They were just raised in the first
resurrection. Right now these saints got
a job to do. Let's go to Psalm 149
and let's see what these saints are
going to be doing
>> at the last day, which is the Lord's
day. Psalm 149.
And we gonna start reading at verse five
because he he he he's he came down from
the third heaven. He called up the dead.
He called up the living. Now they didn't
all met him in the clouds.
>> And he coming back down to the earth. We
just read that in Zechariah 14.
Now these saints got a job to do.
>> Let's read what that is. Psalm 149.
Start reading at verse 5. when you get
it. Go ahead.
>> Let the saints be joyful in glory.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Let them sing aloud upon their beds.
>> So, they gonna be in glory. They gonna
be in their new body by this point in
time. Right. Go ahead. Verse six.
>> Let the high praises of God be in their
mouth.
>> Yeah.
>> And a two-edged sword in their hand.
>> Oh, what you think they going to do with
that sword?
>> Keep reading.
>> To execute vengeance upon the heen
>> and punishment upon the people.
>> So, this ain't no metaphor. You carrying
a sword for real,
>> right? Go ahead. Verse eight.
to bind their kings with chains and
their nobles with feathers of iron.
>> Go ahead.
>> To execute upon them the judgment
written.
>> That's right.
>> Dishonor have all his saints. Praise ye
the Lord.
>> That's one heck of an honor.
>> Yeah.
>> Right.
>> This is what's going to happen at that
day.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. So, he ain't coming by himself.
The saints coming with him. That's
right.
>> And the saints got a job to do.
>> Right. That's why the Lord said in
Revelation 21, don't be fearful.
>> Right. Because if you got a pos, you got
something to take up, then you gonna
have to do your job. And if the and if
the Lord is coming to revenge all
disobedience
>> and you ready to go, then let's get it.
>> Right? Go to Revelation uh 19.
Because what we need to check out
is he got these people coming with him
now, these resurrected beings and these
angels.
Let's see who his opposition is,
right? Because it said they going to
bind up kings. You got to bind up the
kings if he going to be the king. Right.
>> Right. Can't have no other king sitting
beside you.
>> His throne going to be established
forever. So that means that somebody
going to have to be removed from the
premises. Right.
Right.
>> Revelation 19.
We're going to start reading at verse
11. Revelation 19.
Verse 11.
You get it? Go ahead.
>> And I saw heaven opened,
>> and behold, a white horse,
>> and he that sat upon him was called
faithful and true,
>> and in righteousness he doeth judge and
make war.
>> So, nobody ever brings up the fact that
when Jesus come back, he coming to judge
and make war.
>> Right.
>> Right. They be telling us these fairy
tales, he coming, you know, coming back
to rub your back and wipe your tit.
>> Listen.
>> Right.
>> You got to pay. A lot of people going to
be astonished at the last day when this
happened. Yeah. That sky is going to
crack and a lot of people are not gonna
know what's going on. I'm gonna read
that.
>> Keep going. 12.
>> His eyes were as a flame of fire
>> and on his head were many crowns
>> and he had a name written that no man
knew but he himself.
>> It says eyes are like a flame of fire.
Man, you got to think about this.
>> When Israel came I think about things
like Israel came out the uh came out of
Egypt. They sent one time the Lord was
like man I'm about to kill all these
people.
>> What you think he's sitting up there
doing right now looking down at this
earth?
Right.
>> I feel like the the father's probably
like sitting there like holding the mat
like no no no not yet not yet.
>> Right. Cuz by the time he come
>> Yeah.
>> his indignation is going to be full.
>> That's why this day is going to be so
destructive.
>> Right.
>> It says eyes were like a flame of fire.
I mean he probably heeded man.
>> Ask for one thing.
>> Yeah.
>> Just do what I ask you to do.
>> And we find every single way to do the
opposite.
>> Right.
>> Every way. We we will fight tooth and
nail to do the opposite of what God
said.
>> And he's sitting up. He's just sitting
there looking at this thing.
>> Right. So when the Lord let that pit
bull loose,
>> Yeah.
>> that's it.
>> You can't you ain't able to run fast
enough to get from that.
>> Right. Read read verse three.
>> 13.
>> 13. Yes. I'm sorry.
>> And he was clothed with a vest dipped in
blood.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And his name is called the word of God.
>> That ain't no metaphor. It's going to be
blood.
>> You read in Isaiah 63. He said, "I have
tread the wine press alone, and their
blood stained my raignment." Right. Keep
going. 14.
>> And the armies,
>> the what?
>> The armies. Uhhuh. Go ahead.
>> Which were in heaven followed him upon
white horsesh
>> clothed in fine linen, white and clean.
>> Let me tell y'all something. It's a turf
war that everybody has involuntarily
signed themselves up for. This ain't no
bloods and crips. This ain't no uh
uptown verse, downtown, east, west, none
of that. The turf is the earth.
>> And you either in this army
>> or you on the other side.
>> We choose that today.
>> Y'all understand?
>> These armies that followed him are the
resurrected saints and the angels. But
they got an opposition. Skip down to
verse, give me verse 19 and go ahead.
And I saw the beast
>> and the kings of the earth
>> and their armies
>> gather together to make war against him
that sat on the horse and against his
army.
>> So they going to join together and they
going to look up and say, "You want some
of this? Come on."
>> Yeah.
>> That's how crazy man is.
>> Right.
>> They going to see bright lights coming
from the heavens and they going to say,
"We'll fight y'all."
>> Yeah.
>> Cuz man want this earth,
>> right?
>> He They said, "We we the kings here,
>> right? You ain't coming to just take
over what we got.
>> Yeah.
>> Let's go to uh Zephaniah 12. Zechariah
12, I'm sorry. Zechariah chapter 12,
>> man. A wild boy.
>> That's why they try to get you to watch
all these alien movies. Y'all ain't
never seen the alien movie where the
aliens went.
>> No.
>> I mean, where the uh you know, Yeah. the
aliens win. Yeah. Right. Right.
>> It's always man.
>> You know what I'm saying?
>> Yeah.
>> They trying to get you hyped up so that
when they come from the sky, they gonna
be like, "Oh, we got this." Just like
that movie.
>> Yeah. Logan be like, "Ah, yeah, yeah,
okay.
>> This ain't no movie. This ain't
Hollywood,
>> right?" Where y'all think they get all
that that stuff from anyways?
>> Yeah.
>> They take that stuff right out of this
book. But we don't read the book, so we
don't know.
>> Right.
>> We don't know. They they they taking the
script right out of the book.
Zechariah chapter 12.
And we're going to start reading at
verse two. Zechariah chapter 12, verse
two.
You get it? Go ahead and start reading.
>> Behold,
>> I will make Jerusalem a cup of trembling
>> unto all the people round about.
>> Yep.
>> When they shall shall be in the siege
both against Judah and against
Jerusalem.
>> Go ahead.
>> And in that day will I make Jerusalem a
burdensome stone for all people.
>> All that burden themselves with it shall
be cut in pieces.
>> Though all the people of the earth be
gathered together against it.
>> So he said all everybody going to come
up. Everybody gonna get cut to pieces,
>> right? Skip down to verse uh nine and
continue. Go ahead.
>> And it shall come to pass in that day
>> that I will seek to destroy all the
nations that come against Jerusalem.
>> Listen, you got to get your mind right
>> today.
Right. Because the decision on which
side you going to be in this turf war,
you make that today by your actions.
>> Yeah.
>> Right.
But everybody's going to be cut. He
said, he said, "I will seek to destroy
all nations that come up against
Jerusalem."
>> Right? Let's go to Joel chapter 3. Let's
see what Joel saw.
Joel chapter 3,
we're going to start reading at verse 9.
we're going start reading at verse 9.
And the thing is, you got to think about
this.
This how fair the Lord is.
>> He could send an angel and the angel
flap his wings and everybody dropped
dead,
>> right?
>> That's what he did with the Assyrians,
right?
>> 185,000 in one night.
>> Yeah.
>> What the history books say though? Like
a plague came over them.
>> Yeah.
>> Right.
>> But the Lord is smart because he said,
"You know what? I'm coming to take take
your earth, right, that I made for you
because it said he made the earth to be
inhabited.
>> He said, I'm coming to take the earth.
And you know what? I fight you on your
terms.
>> Right.
>> Right. So it ain't going to be no
mistakes.
>> Ain't going ain't going to be no history
books during a thousand year period
talking about it was a plague.
>> Right.
>> It's like nah.
>> The Lord came with the saints and the
angels and they brought swords.
>> Right.
>> Right. Ain't going to be no mistake
about it.
>> Right.
>> That's I mean if you want to fight him,
he gonna give you a fair shot. He
probably laughing at you, but
>> let's see what he say. Joel chapter 3,
pick up verse 9. Go ahead.
>> Proclaim you this among the Gentiles.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Prepare war.
>> Wake up the mighty men.
>> Let all the men of war draw near.
>> Let them come up.
>> I just imagine the Lord sitting there.
Go ahead. Come on. Let's see.
>> Yeah.
>> You know you want to fight. Come on.
Just get everybody get ready.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. Verse 10. Go ahead.
>> Beat your plowshes into swords
>> and your pruning hooks into spears. Let
the weak say, "I am strong."
>> Everybody that want to fight, get your
nuclear weapons, get your missiles, get
your rockets, get all that stuff you
want to get. Just let me know when you
ready.
>> Yeah.
>> Right.
>> Go ahead. 11.
>> Assemble yourselves.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And come
>> all ye heeden
>> and gather yourselves together round
about,
>> right? Thither cause thy mighty ones to
come down,
>> oh Lord.
>> Let the heen be a let the heen be waken
and come up
>> to the valley of Jehoshaphat.
>> Uhhuh.
>> For there will I sit to judge all the
heen roundabout.
>> Go ahead.
>> Put your h put in your sickle
>> for the harvest is ripe.
>> Come get you down for the press is full,
>> the fats overflow for their wickedness
is great.
>> Now this this is uh these men. He said,
"Put in the sickle." Because when you
pulling the harvest, you you know,
pulling up some out of the ground.
>> Yeah.
>> But the that's what's coming out of the
ground is not wicked. It's the men.
>> He's saying, "Put this sickle in the
ground." Uh uh this harvest is great. We
going to clean up a lot of these guys.
Pick up verse 14 and go ahead.
>> Multitudes.
>> Multitudes in the valley of decision.
Right.
>> For the day of the Lord is near in the
valley of decision.
>> The what is near? The day of the Lord.
Because this is the Lord's day. This is
when all this happened. When the Lord
show up, listen man, if you know what's
happening, get your mind right.
>> Keep reading.
>> The sun and the moon shall be darkened.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And the stars shall rejoice the shining.
>> The Lord also shall rule out of Zion
>> and utter his voice from Jerusalem.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And the heavens and the earth shall
shake, but the Lord will be the hope of
his people.
>> Yeah.
>> And the strength of the children of
Israel. Amen. It said that it said that
the Lord shall uh the Lord also shall
roar out of Zion. And um Jeremiah
chapter 4:7, it says uh the lion has
come up out of his thicket.
>> Yeah.
>> You know,
>> you know how the lion sit down from the
uh you know, the deer and all the other
animals and the uh you know, he hide
down in the grass. Now, he done revealed
himself
>> because it don't matter how fast you
think you can run, you ain't getting
away from this,
>> right?
So, we seen that the Lord is going to be
king. It looks like according to what we
can read, he coming to set take this
thing by force. He's coming with the
resurrected saints. He's coming with the
angels and they got some men that they
got to do some business with. Let's go
to Isaiah the 34th chapter and let's
start looking at this actual day. Isaiah
34.
Because even though he gonna be king
over the whole earth, he got to go ahead
and take back his headquarters,
>> right?
He got a headquarters. And right now
they trampling down his headquarters
underfoot.
Isaiah chapter 34,
we're going to start reading at verse
one.
Isaiah chapter 34.
We're going to start reading at verse
one.
>> When you get it, go ahead.
>> Come near.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Ye nations to hear and hearken
>> ye people. Let the earth hear
>> and all that is therein
>> the world and all things that come forth
of it.
>> He's still talking to everybody every
now get get very get a very good
position. I want y'all to hear this
verse two. Go ahead.
>> For the ignation of the Lord is upon all
nations.
>> All nations. Go ahead.
>> And his fury upon all their armies.
>> He had utterly destroyed them.
>> He had delivered them to the slaughter.
>> Go ahead.
>> Their slain also shall be cast out
>> and their stink shall come up out of
their carcasses
>> and the mountain shall be melted with
their blood.
>> He said melted with their blood.
>> Right. You got a slice of cheese and you
melt it. You know what I'm saying?
kind of stick it on anything like poured
on something, right? That's how their
blood going to be
>> on the mountains, right?
>> Man, skip down to verse five and
continue.
>> For my sword shall be bathed in heaven.
>> Behold, it shall come down upon Idumia.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And upon the people of my curse to
judgment.
>> Go ahead.
>> The sword of the Lord is filled with
blood.
>> It is made fat with fattness and with
the blood of the lambs and goats, with
the fat of the kidneys of rams. For the
Lord had a sacrifice in Boatra and a
great salah in the land of Idumia.
>> Keep going.
>> And the unicorn shall come down.
>> This ain't no fantasy thing. The unicorn
is the rhino.
>> Okay. This ain't no pink hair, rainbow
hair, white horse with no rainbow. This
ain't none of that. This ain't no This
ain't no no no game.
>> The Lord ain't playing when he come
back.
>> Right.
>> Go ahead. Read that from the top.
>> Yes. And the unicorn shall come down
with them.
>> Uhhuh. and the bolocks with the bowls
>> and their land shall be soaked with
blood
>> and their dust made fat with fatness.
>> Man, imagine that. We got a uh a new
tree at the house and they've been
telling us to water it every day. I'll
be sitting there like literally just
sitting there watering it,
>> right? Just watching the water fill up
in the ground. He said he said the
ground will be soaked with blood,
>> right?
>> Read verse eight though cuz we going to
see what day it is and we going to see
what he got to handle. Go ahead. For it
is the day of the Lord's vengeance
>> and the year of recompense for the
controversy of Zion.
>> Controversy. I got here a prolonged
public disagreement or debate where
people hold strongly opposing views.
It's a controversy over that land right
now over there.
>> Right. But it says that he's coming to
settle it at that day.
>> Yeah.
>> So I don't care what they got going on
over there. at that day, the day of the
Lord, he's the one that's gonna set it
straight.
>> Y'all understand?
>> Let's go to Jeremiah 25 because he said,
"For the indignation of the Lord is upon
all nations." So, we going to see what
this indignation look like and what's
going to happen here at this day of the
Lord.
Jeremiah 25.
We're gonna read quite a bit of this
because I always look at this is like
the uh the rap sheet chapter. Everybody
the Lord got a he got a list a hit list
and he gonna
hit everybody up.
>> Right. We're gonna see who on the list.
I tell you what, you don't want to be on
this list.
>> No, you don't. Jeremiah 25, we're going
to start reading at verse 15. Jeremiah
25 verse 15. When you get it, go ahead.
>> For thus said the Lord God of Israel
unto me,
>> "Take the wine, take the wine cup of his
of this fury at my hand,
>> and cause all the nation to whom I send
thee to drink it."
>> Uhhuh.
>> And they shall drink
>> and be moved and be mad because the
sword that I will send among them.
then took I the cup at the Lord's hand
and made all the nations to drink unto
whom the Lord had sent me.
>> So he the Lord's like, "Look, man. Um,
everybody going to get a nice good taste
of this wrath." Right?
>> And whoever I tell you that's on this
list,
>> we going to head their way, right? Skip
skip down to verse 19 and continue.
>> Pharaoh, king of Egypt,
>> Uhhuh.
>> and his servants
>> and his princes and all his people.
>> Don't sound like they get in the way. Go
ahead.
>> And all the mingled people.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And all the kings of the land of Osh.
>> Mhm.
>> And all the kings of the land of the
Philistines.
>> Right.
>> And Ashcolon
>> and Azah
>> and Escran and the remnant of Ashdad.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Edom and Moab and the children of Ammon.
>> Now, real quick, you got to think about
this. Do y'all be hearing about people
from any of these nations?
>> No.
>> But they going to be around.
>> Yeah.
>> In some form of fashion. See, people
hide under these country names. The Lord
deal with the names of the families.
>> Right.
>> But these people ain't getting away.
Skip down to verse 24 and continue.
>> And all the kings of the of Arabiah
>> and all the kings of the mingled people
that dwell in the desert.
>> Yeah. He just standing there. Them
people that's back there in the back.
Yeah. Y'all come on up here too.
>> Y'all get a little bit of this. He said
that's mingled in the desert.
>> Yeah.
>> Keep going. Where we at?
>> Skip down to 26.
>> Skip down to 26. I mean, we're skipping
over some of the lists because there's
so many people on the list. The Lord got
a hit list.
>> Yeah.
>> Because you got to think, he just
sitting up there just watching this
entire timeline.
>> Oh my god, I cannot wait.
>> Right.
>> Yeah.
>> Skip down to verse 26 and continue.
>> And all the kings of the north,
>> Uhhuh.
>> far and near,
>> one with another,
>> and all the kingdoms of the world, which
are upon the face of the earth,
>> and the king of Sheekch shall drink
after them. So everybody's gonna have to
drink of this cup,
>> right?
>> He said all and all the kings of the
north, far and near,
>> one with another and all the kingdoms of
the world. Because if he's if it's for
him to be the king, then everybody else
can no longer be king.
>> That's right.
>> And I'm telling you, this man is not
going to give it up easily. He ain't
going to just say, "You know what?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Yes, your highness. Yes, Lord." No, they
ain't gonna do that. They gonna put up a
fight.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. Where we at? 27. Go ahead.
Therefore, thou shalt say unto them,
thus said the Lord of hosts, the God of
Israel, drink ye, and be drunken, and
spew and fall, and rise no more
>> because of the sword which I will send
among you.
>> So, this this is what that wrath is.
Y'all going down as kings and kingdoms.
Y'all not rising anymore.
>> This this it
>> keep going. 28. And it shall be, if they
refuse to take the cup th hand to drink,
>> then shalt thou say unto them,
>> thus said the Lord of hosts, ye shall
certainly drink.
>> You going to drink this cup,
>> right? Yeah.
>> You know how you uh well, you go out
somewhere and uh somebody pouring you a
drink, you like, "Nah, no, I'm I'm good.
I ain't I ain't drinking today." Yeah.
Nah, you you going you gonna drink this.
>> You ain't got This is what's gonna
happen.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. You certainly going to drink the
the cup of this wrath because you cannot
be king,
>> right?
>> I'm the king now.
>> Yeah.
>> And I'm establishing this at my day.
>> Read uh where we at?
>> 29.
>> 29. Go ahead.
>> For lo,
>> I began to bring evil on the city which
is called by my name.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And should ye be utterly unpunished.
>> You see what he said?
>> Yeah.
>> He said, man, you you see what I did to
the people of my own land named after
me? What you think I'm going to do to
y'all?
>> Yeah. You think y'all getting away from
this?
>> Right. Go ahead. Continue that.
>> Ye shall not be unpunished, for I will
call for a sword upon all the
inhabitants of the earth, say the Lord
of hosts.
>> Go ahead.
>> Therefore prophesy thou against them all
these words, and say unto them, the Lord
shall roar from on high, and utter his
voice from his holy habitation.
>> He shall mightily roar upon his
habitation. Amen.
>> He shall give a shout as they that that
tread the grapes against all the
inhabitants of the earth.
>> Go ahead.
>> And noise shall come even to the ends of
the earth.
>> Man,
>> for the Lord had a controversy with the
nations. He will plead with all flesh.
>> It said he got a controversy with
everybody.
>> Now he's coming to settle it at that
day. Keep going.
>> He will give them that wicked to the
sword.
>> That's who going to get the sword.
>> Say the Lord. Sayaith the Lord. that
that's who going to get the sword, the
wicked. See, what what we do in this
world is we like to define what's wicked
so that we can not be wicked.
>> Right.
>> Right. But he defined the wicked. He
defined what that barrier is. Yeah.
>> That's why we got to find out what he
told us to do so that we can make sure
that we on the right side of this thing.
>> That's right.
>> Where we at?
>> 32.
>> Read it.
>> Thus said the Lord of hosts.
>> Behold, evil shall go forth from nation
to nation,
>> and a great whirlwind shall rise up from
the coast of the earth. Go ahead.
>> And the slain of the Lord shall be at
that day from one end of the earth even
unto the other end of the earth.
>> Uhhuh.
>> They shall not be lamented, neither
gathered nor buried. They shall be dung
upon the ground.
>> This don't sound good.
>> Right. The Lord at that day is coming to
strike through the wicked.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. He has to take over the kingship.
And anybody that's following their their
rulership, their leadership, and they
can't let it go, you going right down to
the ground with him. He said it's going
to be dead body spread along the whole
earth. He said, "Ain't nobody going to
cry for you." He said, "You ain't going
to even be buried."
>> Why don't nobody tell us about this
Jesus,
right? Let's go to Isaiah the 13th
chapter.
A lot of people going to be taken by
surprise. That's what we about to read
here. Because nobody is paying attention
to this,
Isaiah the 13th chapter.
You know what they try to do? They try
to go in the Old Testament and say,
"Well, that that Old Testament God, he
was mean. Jesus nice." That's what they
do. They That's what they say. Mhm.
>> You know,
man,
Isaiah 13,
all this happens at that day. Isaiah 13,
we will start reading at verse 6. Isaiah
13.
Verse 6. When you get it, go ahead.
>> Hold ye for the day of the Lord is at
hand. Mhm.
>> It shall come as a destruction from the
Almighty.
>> The day of the Lord is at hand. This is
the Lord's day. It keeps telling you
what that day is.
>> I ain't read Sunday yet,
>> right?
>> No.
>> This ain't got nothing to do with
Sunday.
>> Right. Read verse seven. Go ahead.
>> Therefore shall all hands be faint
>> and every man's heart shall melt.
>> He said every cuz even if you know
what's going on,
>> that's a scary time.
>> Yeah,
>> that's a scary time. You can know. You
can know this book up and down, back and
forth. But when the Lord cracked that
sky,
>> man, that's a fearful time.
>> It said, "All hands shall be faint.
Every man's heart shall melt." Read that
verse eight. Go ahead.
>> And they shall be afraid.
>> Pangs and sorrow shall take hold of
them.
>> They shall be in pain as a woman that
travail.
>> They shall be amazed one at another.
>> Their faces shall be as flames. I'm
telling you, people gonna be passing
out.
>> And you think about this,
>> yeah, heart attacks.
>> Um, you think about this,
>> you know what's going on. What about the
people that don't know what's going on,
>> right?
>> They're going to be passing. Hey, what
is happening?
>> This is not what they told me.
>> You going to find out at that day.
>> Yeah.
>> But we got to get in order now. Skip
down to verse uh 11 and continue.
>> And I will punish the world for their
evil
>> and the wicked for their iniquity. See,
this this where it goes back to because
yeah, he got to take down the kings, but
he got to take down the wicked for their
iniquity.
>> So, that's why it's so important to find
somewhere where they're teaching you
what this iniquity is. What is this sin?
Because we make up in our own mind what
sin is,
>> right?
Read that from the top.
>> And I will punish the world for their
evil and the wicked for their iniquity.
Uh-huh.
>> And I will cause the arrogancy of the
proud to cease
>> and will lay low the hardiness of the
terrible.
>> Amen. Let's go to uh Zephaniah chapter
1.
>> Just showing y'all what's going to
happen at this day.
>> Zephaniah chapter 1.
And the Lord in Matthew 24, he said, uh,
only my father in heaven know when that
time is going to be.
>> Yeah. So he just sitting there just
waiting, waiting, waiting. The Lord go.
>> Yeah.
>> He gonna let him loose.
>> Exactly.
Um Zephaniah chapter 1.
>> We going to start reading at verse 14.
Zephaniah chapter 1 verse4. People tell
you know, don't even turn to the Old
Testament. That's all fulfilled. Boy,
are they going to be in for a rude
awakening. A rude awakening.
Zephaniah 1 verse14. Go ahead.
>> The great day of the Lord is near.
>> Everything keeps telling you about the
day of the Lord. It's It's Think about
this. It's You have to mess this up on
purpose. It takes you energy to mess
this up. It keeps telling you what it
is.
The great day of the Lord is near. Go
ahead.
>> It is near.
>> Uhhuh. and hasted greatly even the voice
of the day of the Lord.
>> Go ahead.
>> The mighty man shall cry bitterly.
>> He said, "The mighty man shall cry
bitterly." Go ahead.
>> The day The day is a day of wrath,
>> a day of trouble and distress, a day of
wastess and desolation,
>> a day of darkness and glooiness, a day
of clouds and thick darkness.
>> Thick darkness. That's a dark dark day
>> when the Lord returned.
>> Yeah.
>> Go ahead.
a day of the trumpet and alarm against
the fence cities and against the high
towers.
>> What's that scripture that say you um
you know shall a shall a trumpet be
blown in the city and the people not be
afraid? You know how loud that horn is
going to be for the whole world to hear
it?
>> Yeah.
>> If people
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> It's a terrifying sound.
>> Terrifying. Go ahead.
>> 17.
>> Uhhuh. And it will bring distress upon
men
>> that they shall walk like blind men
>> because they have sinned against the
Lord.
>> Amen.
>> And their blood shall be poured out as
dust and their flesh as dung.
>> Man, go ahead, finish that.
>> Neither their silver nor their gold
shall be able to deliver them in the day
of the Lord's wrath.
>> And Lord don't care about how much money
you got. Lord don't care how many
degrees you got and how much success and
businesses you got. Ain't nobody ask you
all that. The Lord just want to know,
did you do what I asked you to do?
>> Yeah. That's all we dealing with. Did
you follow the instructions?
You see, if your business isn't your
money, have your own business and you
know,
>> Yeah.
>> But people trust in those things.
>> They can't deliver you, right?
>> Go ahead.
>> But the whole land shall be devoured by
the fire of his jealousy.
>> Uhhuh.
>> For he shall make even a speedy riddance
of all them that dwell in the land. He
>> said he gonna make a speedy riddance.
Right. Go to Isaiah chapter 2.
Isaiah chapter 2.
We going to walk out of here with a
very, very good understanding of what to
expect when the Lord cracks that sky.
That don't mean that you ain't going to
be afraid. All I'm saying is that we
gonna have a good understanding of
what's going to happen, right? Mhm.
>> And what we about to read about here is,
you know, for these men that don't know
what's going on, or even for the ones
that do that think they got a way of
escape,
>> we going to see if they got a way of
escape.
Isaiah chapter 2,
we going to start reading at verse 10.
Isaiah chapter 2, verse 10. When you get
it, go ahead. Enter into the rock
>> and hide thee in the dust for fear of
the Lord. For the glory of his majesty,
>> the lofty looks of men shall be humbled,
>> and the hardiness of men shall be bowed
down,
>> and the Lord alone shall be exalted in
that day.
>> Go ahead.
>> For the day of the Lord of hosts shall
be upon everyone that is proud and
lofty, and upon everyone that is lifted
up, and he shall be brought low. You got
these people that walk around chest up,
chin up, real high, real proud at that
day.
>> The Lord ain't don't care about none of
that.
>> Did you do what I asked you to do or you
going to be sat down, right?
But it's all happening at that day. Skip
down to verse 17 and continue.
>> And the loftiness of men shall be bowed
down
>> and the hardiness of men shall be made
low
>> and the Lord alone shall be exalted in
that day. It's going to be one king and
it's going to be him.
>> Right. Keep uh skip down to 19. Go
ahead.
>> And they shall go into the holes of the
rocks
>> and into the caves of the earth
>> for fear of the Lord and for the glory
of his majesty when he ariseth to shake
terrible the earth.
>> Why? Why y'all hiding in these rocks all
of a sudden?
>> Because that's how man, you know, man
operate. He stick his chest up. He stick
his chin up. I run this earth,
>> right? But when the big dogs show up,
>> now you want to start doing all this
hot,
>> right?
>> 20.
>> In that day, a man shall cast his idols
of silver
>> and his idols of gold.
>> You see, that's just idols. They worship
this stuff, their money and their
possessions and all that stuff. Go
ahead.
>> Which they made each one for himself to
worship
>> to the moles and to the bats.
>> And at that point in time, they g they
going to say, "Get rid of it." Right?
>> Go ahead. to go into the cliffs of the
rocks and into the tops of the ragged
rocks for fear of the Lord and for the
glory of his majesty when he ariseth to
shake terrible the earth.
>> Finish that.
>> Cec see from man whose breath is in his
nostril. For where for wherein is he to
be counted off? This is gonna be a tough
day for the proud and the hardy and the
lofty
>> because the one number one thing that
you have to do to especially come into a
place and let somebody actually teach
you what the Bible says. You got to
humble yourself. It says in Revelation
chapter 12 that the devil has deceived
the whole world. But you'll tell and and
the thing is you'll take that to
somebody and say, "Look, it says right
here, the devil deceived the whole
world." I ain't been deceived.
>> That's what they'll say.
>> I ain't been deceived.
>> I think you've been deceived because you
in a cult.
>> Right.
The Lord g he going he gonna figure all
that stuff out for everybody. That's why
I be telling look don't go back and
forth with people because it may be that
somebody may not have humbled themselves
right now.
>> Maybe they will before the last day,
>> right? So we got to have grace with
people. But these people here are the
ones that even down to the end.
>> Yeah.
>> They walking around proud. Their chin is
up. Their chest is up. They say this
mine,
>> right?
>> This earth is mine. I run this.
>> But when the Lord show up, they gonna be
trying to hide. Let's go to Amos chapter
5.
I don't know what's going to be in their
mind that going to allow them to think
that, oh, this one that's coming down
that can see literally everything. He's
not going to know I'm h I'm trying to
hide in this rock.
>> I'm trying to hide in this cave.
>> Right? Nobody's getting away from this.
It said that the Lord got a controversy
with all nations, with everybody and the
wicked, right? That's why it's so
important to get that understanding. Who
is the wicked? Right?
Amos chapter 5, we're going to start
reading
verse 18. Amos chapter 5, verse 18. When
you get it, go ahead.
>> Woe unto you that desire the day of the
Lord. Woe unto you that desire the day
of the Lord.
>> Go ahead.
>> To what end is it for you?
>> The day of the Lord is darkness and not
light.
>> This is This ain't a day that's going to
be pleasant on this earth.
>> It's a dark day.
>> I remember I was at like a uh it's like
a conference or something like that one
time and this uh this lady stood up and
she said, "You know, I'm just waiting
for the day my Lord and Savior returns
and takes me off." And I'm just like,
man, you don't even you don't know what
you're asking. You don't know what you
asking,
>> right? Read 19. Let's see who going to
get away from it.
>> As if a man did flee from a lion
>> and a beer met him.
>> So it says like you running from a lion
>> and you didn't got away from the lion.
You
>> man.
>> Yeah,
>> that was close.
>> And it's a bear right there.
>> A grizzly,
>> right? Keep reading. Go ahead. or went
into the house
>> and leave his hand on the wall and a
serpent bit him.
>> So you know you done got home now you
>> goodness gracious that was close.
>> Then a serpent bites you. You're not
getting away.
>> Yeah.
>> The Lord is trying to tell you every
single form or fashion so that you can
understand this. You're not getting
away.
>> Read verse 20. Go ahead.
>> Shall not the day of the Lord be
darkness and not light even very dark
>> and no brightness in it?
>> It's no brightness in that day. It's a
dark day. Right. Even like I said, even
if you understand and know what's going
on, that's a scary time, man. You know,
when you start hearing them trumpets
that the whole world can hear, you know
how loud that got to be?
>> Smoke everywhere. The lights then then
stop working. Imagine sitting right here
and the sun was just like, I'm going go
ahead and take a rest.
>> Darkness.
>> Yeah.
>> Right.
>> Let's look and see how dark it's going
to be. Let's go back to Isaiah 13 now.
Isaiah 13.
Should have told you I put a marker
here. Good.
Isaiah 13. We going to start reading at
verse nine. Everything keeps telling you
throughout this book what's going to
happen at the day of the Lord. It's a
dark day. It's a terrible day. Waste,
desolation,
spoil,
right? This is the Lord's day.
Isaiah 13, we're going to start reading
at verse nine. When you get it, go ahead
and read it.
>> Behold, the day of the Lord cometh.
>> Go ahead.
>> Cruel both with wrath and fierce anger
>> to lay the land desolate,
>> and he shall destroy the sinners
>> thereof out of it.
>> Go ahead.
>> The for the stars of heaven and the
constellation thereof shall not give
their light.
>> Uhhuh.
>> The sun shall be darkened in his going
forth,
>> and the moon shall not cause a light to
shine. So every time you read about this
const these constellations, the sun, the
moon, the stars not giving it light,
this is the same time period.
>> This is the Lord's day. Let's go to uh
Joel chapter 2.
Keeps telling you over and over and
over,
but we don't believe it. This when
people don't believe stuff like this, I
mean, that's that's what unbelief is. We
don't believe what's written, and we
love for some man to come and tell us
really what we want to hear. That's all
we want to hear. We just want to hear
what we want to hear and go about our
merry way. As soon as we get in our car,
you just go back to doing whatever you
want to do,
>> right?
Joel chapter 2,
we'll start reading at verse 30. Joel
chapter 2, verse 30.
When you get it, go ahead.
>> And I will show wonders in the heavensh
>> and in the earth,
>> blood and fire and pillars of smoke,
>> the sun shall be turned into darkness
>> and the moon into blood. Mhm.
>> before the great and terrible day of the
Lord come.
>> You know, even on the uh the darkest
day, the sun is shining.
>> Yeah.
>> Just got cloud cover.
>> Can you imagine there's no light coming
from the sun,
>> right? That's what's going to happen at
the Lord's day. Go to uh Matthew 24.
Let's see what Jesus say about it.
Because, you know, they'll they'll say,
"Well, you know, that was something that
happened and you know, somebody got a
whole YouTube section on it." And I told
you, man. People just make up stuff,
man.
>> They need to rename YouTube getyoulosun
university.com.
That's what it is. Go on there and we
get lost. This book got all the words
right here. We want to go just hear
people talk.
Matthew 24. We're going to read one
verse here.
Matthew 24 verse 29. You get it. Go
ahead.
>> Immediately after the tribulation of
those days
>> shall the sun be darkened
>> and the moon shall not give a light.
>> Right?
>> And the stars shall fall from heaven
>> and the powers of the heaven shall be
shaken.
>> So Jesus is telling you the same thing
>> we're dealing with today. We're not
dealing with the great tribulation.
We're dealing with the day of the Lord.
>> The Lord's day, right? You know, it's
like uh the great tribula, like the Lord
was saying, he said immediately after
the tribulation of those days because we
about to go into some of these seals and
these seals are open during the great
tribulation,
>> right? But you know how you go to a
concert and you got like the opening
act, you know, they come out, you know,
they might be good, might be bad, have
might have two or three,
>> but when the main event come, what they
do? They shut the lights off.
>> Right.
>> Boom.
>> And now the main attraction is on the
scene. Yeah. And that's how it's going
to be when the Lord come. He going to
shut the lights off
>> and everybody's going to be focused on
him,
right? Let's go to Revelation 6.
Man,
no matter how you try to play this out
in your mind, you cannot picture this. I
was going to try to put up some uh like
some imagery, but you you you can't
imagine it,
>> right? We've never seen anything that's
gonna come up like this that's gonna
come upon this earth.
>> Revelation six.
So what we're about to read here, if you
go into Revelation 5, there's a book
with seven seals on it. Okay?
And the lamb is the only one that can
open these seals. Now, most of these
seals are open during the great
tribulation. As I just said, we not
dealing with the great tribulation
today. So we going to jump to the end of
the great tribulation and we gonna start
dealing with the Lord's day. Amen.
Revelation 6. We're going to start
reading verse 12. So we jumping down to
the sixth seal. Revelation 6 verse 12.
When you get it, go ahead and start
reading it.
>> And I beheld.
>> Mhm.
>> When he had opened the sixth seal,
>> and lo, there was a great earthquake.
Yeah.
>> And the sun became black as sackcloud of
here, and the moon became as blood.
>> Go ahead.
>> And the stars of heaven fell unto the
earth,
>> even as a fig tree casted her untimely
figs.
>> When she's shaking of a mighty wind.
>> Go ahead. And the heavens departed as a
scroll when it is rolled together
>> and every mountain and island move out
of their places.
>> So he said that the the heavens he said
going to depart as a scroll.
>> Know you got a scroll and you know you
kind of let that thing down.
>> The heaven is going to sit there like a
curtain just going to roll back.
>> Yeah.
>> Cuz right now you look up what you see
clouds.
>> You see the constellations,
>> right? He said that's going to move
back.
>> Yeah.
>> Because you got to be able to see him.
We had kept reading that Matthew 24.
says everybody going to see him.
>> Right.
>> Where you at?
>> 15.
>> Read it.
>> And the kings of the earth
>> and the great men
>> and the rich men and the chief captains
and the mighty men and every bondman and
every free man hid themselves in the
dens and in the rocks of the mountains.
>> Let me tell you something. If you alive
at this time,
>> drop down to your knees and start
praying,
>> right?
>> Yeah. Try to recollect something in your
mind that the Lord might want to repay
you for
>> that you might have forgot
and seek forgiveness,
>> right? Go ahead.
>> 16
>> and said to the mountains and the rocks,
fall on us.
>> So now they want the rocks to kill him.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. Go ahead.
Go ahead.
>> And hide us from the face of him that
sitted upon the throne.
>> Then the thing is he ain't even take the
throne yet. He ain't come down.
>> Yeah.
>> All he did was show up. Yeah. He just
turned the lights off and said, "Hey,
hey guys."
>> Yeah.
>> Right.
>> Read.
>> And from the wrath of the lamb.
>> Nobody talks about the wrath of the
lamb.
>> 17.
>> For the great day of his wrath is come.
And who shall be able to stand?
>> Not a lot of people. That's what we've
been reading, right?
>> Yeah.
>> We're going to go over to Revelation
chapter 8 and we going to actually go
through what's going to happen at the
Lord's day. Revelation chapter 8.
And we going to start at verse one. We
actually just going to read this. Yeah.
We going we going we going to talk this
through. Revelation chapter 8. Start
reading at verse one. Go ahead.
>> And when he had opened the seven seals
>> Uhhuh.
>> there was silence in heaven about the
space of an half half hour.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And I saw the seven angels which stood
before God. And to them were given seven
trumpets.
>> Now these the ones that's going to blow
these trumpets. Right now, we gonna read
about what's going to happen when these
trumpets sound.
>> Um, we not going to do the vows. So, you
know, for most of uh us to know that
when there is a trumpet sounded, there's
a vow that's poured down on the earth.
>> And the way Revelation reads is like if
you sitting there, it's almost like you
got a bird's eye view of the angel
that's blowing the trumpet and the and
the angel that's pouring down the vow
and you just like, man,
>> oh, that look bad down there. Yeah.
That's how that's how this that's how
Revelation kind of read.
>> You know, you gonna be able to see all
these things that happened on the earth.
Now, if you on the earth and you got
that point of view, it's like, man, this
is this rough.
>> Yeah.
>> Right.
>> So, we're gonna read about what's going
to happen at the Lord. All we've been
reading all day is about the Lord's day.
>> Yeah.
>> Right.
Read verse three. Go ahead.
>> And another angel came and stood at the
altar
>> having a golden center.
>> And there was given unto him much
incense
>> that he should offer it with the prayers
of all the saints upon the golden altar
which was before the throne.
>> Go ahead. And the smoke of the incense
which came with the prayers of the
saints ascended up before God out of the
angel's hand.
>> And the angels took the sensor and fill
it with fire of altar and cast it into
the earth.
>> And there were voices and thundering and
lightning and earthquakes.
>> So you got again just think about the
vantage point I just gave you. You
sitting there, you watching. It says the
angel took the sensor, filled it with
fire of the altar and cast it to the
earth. So that angel's probably like
light this on fire. Boom. Throw it down
there. But you on earth like what? You
know what is going on.
>> And if you don't read this book, then
you're not going to know.
>> Keep reading verse six.
>> And the seven angel which had the seven
trumpet prepared them prepared
themselves to sound. So when they opened
up the seven seal, you had seven seven
angels lined up that has seven trumpets
and they like I said corresponding there
are angels with seven vows as well. So
as we go through these I'll just tell
you when this angel trump when this
trumpet sound where you can read and
what's going to happen when that vow is
poured out. So we going to read verse
seven when this first angel sounds. Go
ahead. The first angel sounded
>> uh
>> and they followed hail and fire mingle
with blood
>> and they were cast upon the earth and
the third part of the the trees were
burned up and all green grass was burned
up.
>> You going um I think it's Job the 38th
chapter and the Lord and Job said in
that uh 23rd and 24th verse that that
hell is reserved for the day of the Lord
and he's dropping it right here on that
first trumpet sounding right now. And
you go into Revelation 16 and2 and that
first vow is poured out. So every time a
trumpet sounds, something happens. Every
time a vow is poured out, something
happens. Right? Keep reading. Where you
at?
>> Oh, that was the end of seven.
>> Read eight.
>> And the second angel sounded
>> and as it were a great mountain burning
with fire
>> was cast into the sea
>> and the third part of the sea became
blood. So in Revelation 16 verse uh
three it says the second angel poured
out his vow upon the sea and it became
uh blood as of a dead man. Same thing
somebody sounding the trumpet somebody's
pouring out a vow but on the earth we
don't know what's going on. If you don't
read this book all you just see is like
man what is going on? And I imagine we
know because we've been reading. What if
you don't know? You going to think this
what is happening right now? You might
think you dreaming. You going to try to
do everything. You stomping on your own
foot, pinching yourself, smacking
yourself. This got to be faith.
>> Yeah.
>> Cuz this these these are unnatural
things,
>> right? Where we at?
>> Verse nine.
>> Read it.
>> And the third part of the creatures
which were in the sea and had life died.
>> And the third part of the ships were
destroyed.
>> Go ahead. And the third angel sounded,
and there fell a great star from heaven,
>> burning as it were a lamp, and it fell
upon the third part of the rivers, and
upon the fountains of water.
>> So when you go into Revelation 16:4, it
says in the third angel poured out his
vow upon the rivers and fountains of
water, and they became blood. No. Yes.
So this this star that came down made
the waters uh actually read that next
verse. And the names of the star is
called wormwood.
>> And the third part of the waters became
wormwood. And many men died of the water
because they were made bitter.
>> So you got all this stuff. Imagine you
going to be running too. You're going to
be running now. You can't drink the
water,
>> right? You drink the water, you're going
to die. This this is this is I mean this
is hell on earth,
>> right?
>> Keep going. Verse 12. And the fourth
angel sounded, and the third part of the
sun was smitten, and the third part of
the moon, and the third part of the
stars,
>> so as the third part of them was
darkened,
>> and the day shown not for a third part
of it, and the and the night likewise,
>> darkness again, right? Same thing. You
go to Revelation 16 8 and 9. This
trumpet sounds, he's pouring out that
vow. Read that 13. And I beheld and
heard an angel flying through the midst
of the heaven saying with a loud voice,
"Woe, wo, woe to the inhabitants of the
earth by reason of the other voices of
the trumpet of the three angels which
are yet to sound."
>> So there's three more trumpets that need
to be sounded. And he's saying, "Look,
these three going to bring this final
destruction of the day of the Lord."
>> Keep going right into Revelation 9.
>> We're going to start reading verse one.
Go ahead. And the fifth angel sounded,
>> and I saw a star far from heaven unto
the earth, and to him was given the key
of the bottomless pit,
>> right?
>> And he opened the bottomless pit, and
there arose a smoke out of the pit
>> as a smoke of a great furnace.
>> And the sun and the ear was darkened by
reason of the smoke of the pit.
>> So you got to think, man, all this stuff
is going on. John is seeing this in the
vision because remember what it said in
Revelation 1:10. He said, "I was in a
vision on the Lord's day."
>> Yeah. The Lord's day is the last day.
>> He just writing all this stuff down.
>> Yeah.
>> But for his time, they, you know, they
walking around in tunics and, you know,
probably some sandals. I'm guessing he
probably had like the thing where you
>> you dipped it in there so he could
write. Dip the ink.
>> You know what I'm saying? So he can
write.
>> He just He's looking beyond our time
today.
>> He's trying to describe in his mind the
best way he what he know look like
locust coming up out of there.
>> Right.
But I mean all every time I read through
this, I'm just thinking, man, it's gonna
be dark smoke everywhere,
>> blood waters. Uh you can't drink the
water that's not blood.
>> This is this this is this is this is
terrifying,
>> right?
>> Um
>> verse three,
>> read it.
>> And they came out of the smoke locust
upon the earth.
>> Uhhuh. And unto them was given power as
a scorpion of the earth have power.
>> And it was commanded them that they
should not hurt the the grass of the
earth.
>> Neither any green thing, neither any
tree, but only those men which have not
the seal of God in the forehead.
>> Yeah, we skipped over them getting
sealed in Revelation 7. So all this
destruction is going for this particular
time is going to happen in a particular
area. And this is what's going to start
kicking off what we're calling World War
II. I think it's close enough to me at
least to be at the end where this is
probably going to be World War II.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. Keep reading verse 5.
>> And to them it was given that they
should not kill them
>> but that they should be tormented five
months.
>> And their torment was as the torment of
a scorpion when he striketh a man.
>> I was actually in um that's funny how we
read that. I didn't think about this. I
was actually in Arizona this week and in
the desert and uh I was in Sedona and uh
you know they warned us about all the
things to look out for rattlesnakes and
scorpions and all these things. So I'm
sitting there looking for these things.
I don't want to get stung by no scor no
scorpion, right? So when I'm going out
to like do my walk, I'm sitting there.
I'm like making sure that it's clear
coverage from the bushes and I don't
want nothing jumping out on me. Right?
But this thing say you going to be
tormented for five months. And their
torment was as a as a torment of a
scorpion that strike for man for five
months. Right. Read verse six. Go ahead.
>> And in those days shall men seek death
and shall not find it
>> and shall desire to die and death shall
flee from death.
>> That's that's horrible.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm tormented so bad that I want to die.
>> He ain't going to let you die.
>> Skip down to verse uh 13. And that fifth
angel, you read that uh the fifth vow.
You read that in Revelation 16 10- 11.
We going to skip down to 13. Um, now
read that. Go ahead.
>> And the six angels sounded.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And I heard a voice from the four horns
of the golden altar which is before God.
>> Right.
>> Saying to the six angel which had the
trumpet, loose the four angels which are
bound in the great river Euphrates.
>> Uhhuh. and the four angels were loosed
which were prepared for an hour and a
day and a month and a year for to slay
the third part of men.
>> So you got angels that's just sitting at
the Euphrates River
>> waiting.
>> They just waiting
>> for the day of the Lord and this
particular time so they can dry up this
river. Yeah.
>> So that the men from the west from the
east can cross over to the west
>> and that's going to cause that war.
>> Right. Read that next verse. 17
>> 16
>> 16 And the number of the armies of the
horsemen were 200,000,000.
And I heard the number of them.
>> 200,000,000.
>> That's a lot of people.
>> Yeah.
>> Going to be coming from east to west.
When you read this in Revelation 16, it
says, "The sixth angel poured out his
vow upon the great river Euphrates, and
the water thereof was dried up that the
way of the kings of the east might be
prepared.
>> And they coming to make war." 200
million
>> million
>> coming to make war.
>> So not only is the Lord sending all this
catastrophe down on the earth, now you
got serious war. Them little scrimmages
and you know them little pity pat stuff
they got going on right now that ain't
none compared to this.
>> This is this this this is scrimmage.
This is practice,
>> right?
>> 17
>> 17 uh no, skip down to verse uh 20
because I and I wanted to get to this
part because even Still at that point,
man still man still
is going to be stuck in his wickedness.
Read verse 20. Go ahead.
>> And the rest of the men which were not
killed by these plagues.
>> SO YOU DIDN'T SURVIVED up to this point.
You see all this stuff happening and you
didn't survived, right? Keep reading.
yet repented not of the works of their
hands,
>> that they should not worship the devil,
>> and idols of gold, and of silver, and of
brass, and stone, and of wood, which
neither can see, nor hear nor walk.
>> Keep reading.
>> Neither repented they of their murders,
nor of their sorceries, nor of the
fornication, nor of thefts.
>> What you want me to say?
>> The Lord is justified in this. when he
come back this he's the he's the gonna
be because we done read about how many
people he gonna kill this gonna be
righteous killings
>> these people don't care about God they
don't care about nothing he said to do
>> and even after seeing all this
destruction and the Lord let them live
to that point
I ain't doing it
>> I ain't doing that
>> that's what they going to be dealing
with kind of spirit got to be in these
people's mind
right
>> let's go to uh Revelation 11.
Revelation 11.
And we going to see what happens when
the seventh trumpet is sound because
there's only seven trumpets and he comes
on the last one. Right.
>> Revelation 11. We're going to start
reading at verse 15. Revelation 11.
Verse 15. When you get it, go ahead. And
the seven angels sounded,
>> and there were great voices in heaven,
saying, "The kingdoms of this world are
become the kingdom of our Lord
>> and of his Christ, and he shall reign
forever and ever."
>> So that's what we that's what this whole
day of the Lord was about.
>> And that's why we read all that stuff
about him becoming king, him grabbing
the saints, him grabbing the angels. It
was to establish his kingdom here on the
earth. And when that seventh trumpet
sounds, that's it.
>> Right? Keep reading 16. And the four the
four and 20 elders which sat before God
and their seat fell upon their faces and
worshiped God, saying, We give thee
thanks, O Lord Almighty, which art and
was and are to come.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Because thou hast taken to thee thy
great power and has reigned.
>> Go ahead.
>> And the nations were angry.
>> You see, they they angry because they
don't want him to come take over this
earth. They want to keep running it. And
now they see the seventh trumpet, he's
coming down. They like, "All right,
well, come on then." All right, go
ahead.
>> And the nations were angry.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And thy wrath has come.
>> And the time of the dead, that they
should be judged,
>> right?
>> And that thou shouldest give reward unto
thy servants, the prophets, and to the
saints, and them that fear thy name,
small and great,
and shouldest destroy them which destroy
the earth.
>> So these people that's been destroying
the earth all these years,
>> it's payday.
Now, that's the day of the Lord.
Did anybody read Sunday?
>> No.
Right. I didn't. Right.
So, one thing y'all gonna learn about me
is that I'm a wise person.
So, where did it come from? Right.
First, let's go to Mark chapter 7 and
then we gonna pull up some receipts
right quick and then we gonna close it
out. Mark chapter 7. Cuz
men got their own traditions and they
love them. They cannot let these
traditions go.
Mark chapter 7
and we going to start reading at verse
6. Mark chapter 7
verse 6.
When you get it, go ahead and start
reading.
>> He answered and said unto them,
>> Uhhuh.
>> Well, that Isaiah prophesied of you
hypocrites
>> as it is written, "This people honor me
with their their lips, but their heart
is far from me."
>> Go ahead.
>> How be it in vain do they worship me,
teaching for doctrines the commandments
of men.
>> Man,
>> for that's good. We we know somebody
like this.
>> He said, you know, you you honor me with
your lips, but your mind is somewhere
else, and you always want to deal with
the commandments of men. Skip down to
verse nine and continue. And he said
unto them, "Full well you reject the
commandments of God, that ye may keep
your own traditions."
>> That's what you trying to do. Skip down
to verse 13.
>> Making the word of God of none effect
through your traditions
>> which ye have delivered and many such
like things ye do.
>> It said you you making the word of God
of none effect. So when you try to tell
somebody, man, Sunday's not the Lord's
day. They say, "Yeah, yeah, it is the
Lord's day." and you done read all this
stuff about all these things that's
going to happen at that particular day
and they say, "Nah, man.
>> Lord's day is Sunday. I don't know what
you've been learning about."
>> Where they get it from Dez, you ready?
Let's do it.
All right. So, we got a little bit of
history here. What we going to show is
at three different points in history
where they have identified the Lord's
day as Sunday. The first one here is the
dedic dedic and brother Donnie is going
to read what that means. So, we're going
to read what this means first and then
we're going to read the excerpt out of
this particular um this particular book.
>> Didachi 90 to 110 ADA pronounced dedi
>> is the Greek word for the teaching. Its
full title is the Lord's teaching to the
12 apostles to the nations.
>> So, take take note of this time period.
This time period is roughly around the
time when the apostles died. This is
what is called postappostolic teaching.
So this is right around after the
apostles died. This is what they started
to teach the people. Right. Um where you
at?
>> And
>> go ahead.
>> And it is considered one of the oldest
Christian doc documents in existence
>> outside of the scripture itself.
>> But you don't need anything else besides
the scripture.
>> But they like to add in other things and
teach things their own way.
>> Right.
>> Right. Go ahead. It f it functioned
essentially as the first written
catechism of the early church containing
instructions and baptism, fasting, the
eukarist and how to receive traveling
teachers.
>> This is so this is them setting up their
own church rules.
>> Right now we actually now you you got
some more to read. We're going to
actually see what's in the the
>> dedicay
>> um chapter 14 verse one. What does it
say? On the Lord's own day, gather
together and break bread and offer
thanks, having first confessed your
transgression, so that your sacrifice
may be pure.
>> So, this is one of the first places
where they have identified this as the
Lord's day, right?
>> Go to the next one. Now, we didn't read
this one before. This is canon 29. This
is from the canon of Leia Deia uh 363
364. Read that excerpt. This is so canon
is their laws.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. So what we're about to read is
their uh their church law canon 29. Go
ahead.
>> Christians must not Judaize by resting
on the Sabbath.
>> Uhhuh.
>> But must work on that day.
>> You must work on the Sabbath day. Go
ahead.
>> Rather honoring the Lord's day.
>> They said, "No, you're supposed to honor
the Lord's day because the Lord's day is
Sunday. You honor that." And and and and
what did they do? Not only did they they
write this stuff down as a part of their
church doctrine, they went and they took
you to your lands and they taught you
this stuff
>> and they taught your fathers this stuff
and they taught their fathers this stuff
over and over and over. And then you
know what happens when you get older?
Nah, man. I've been doing this my whole
life.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. Go ahead.
>> And if they can resting then as
Christians.
>> But
>> so you're a Christian if you rest on the
Lord's day.
>> Yeah.
>> That's what they saying. Go ahead. But
if any shall be found to be Judaizers,
let them be an anatomy anime anithma
from Christ.
>> Or curse from Christ. So they said, "You
keep the Sabbath, you curse from
Christ." Right now, we going to read
another excerpt here, but I got to hear
what is a catechism because it was
actually in the uh the dedicay, but
we're going to read what a catechism is.
And we're going to read an excerpt out
of the Catholic the catechisms of the
Catholic Church. So read what is a
catechism? a summary of principles
especially of religious doctrines often
in the form of questions and answers.
>> So the way they got this set up is that
they set up these rules and they got
commentaries under these rules and this
is what they will teach you. This is
what was taught to our ancestors so much
so that that we fight tooth and nail as
we get older when somebody bring us
these real words out of this book.
Right? So we're going to read two cate
you got to read this out of the book.
So, I actually got this book. Anybody
want to come take pictures of the book
afterwards? Because what is on here is
going to be the actual rule, the actual
catechism. So, the actual principle that
they have, this is what they use to
teach the people. Now, the reason he's
going to read it out of the book is
because I actually put the rule on here.
What you can see here is that article
three, this is the third commandment,
section two, the Lord's Day, uh,
catechism of the Catholic Church. This
is catechism 2174.
Now, the way that this book is
structured is that this is the catechism
2174, but in addition to the catechism,
it also has commentary. Now, I didn't
put the commentary on the slide. So,
he's going to read the catechism and
he's going to read the uh commentary. Go
ahead.
>> The Lord's day.
>> Uhhuh.
>> This is the day which the Lord has made.
>> Let us rejoice and be glad in it.
>> The day of the resurrection, the new
creation. 2174. Jesus rose from the dead
on the first day of the week.
>> Because it is the first day, the day of
Christ. Resurrection recalls the first
creation because it is the eighth day
following the Sabbath. It symbolizes the
new creation ushered in by Christ's
resurrection. For Christian, it has
become the first of all days, the first
of all feast, the Lord's day.
>> Just Sunday. You ain't got to read that
parenthesis. So he said they said that
the Lord's day has become the first of
all feasts.
>> Yeah.
>> Right.
>> Read the commentary there though.
>> We all gather on that day.
>> We we all we all gather on the day of
the sun.
>> For it is the first day.
>> Go ahead.
>> After the Jewish Sabbath,
>> but also the first day when God
separated matter from darkness,
>> made the world. And on this same day,
Jesus Christ, our savior, rose from the
dead.
>> So they said, we gather on the day of
the sun, but they call that the Lord's
day. They said that's the greatest of
all the feasts, right? Let me get that
next slide, D.
So now we're going to read catechism
2175.
>> Go ahead.
>> Sunday, fulfillment of the Sabbath.
>> 2175. Sunday is especially expressly
distinguished from the Sabbath, which is
followed chronologically every week.
Mhm.
>> For Christians, it it ceremonial
observance replaces that of the Sabbath
>> in Christ Passover. Sunday fulfills the
spirit.
>> Spiritual truth.
>> Mhm.
>> Yeah.
>> The spiritual truth of the Jewish
Sabbath and announces man's eternal rest
in God.
>> Well, the last time I checked, the Lord
said that uh when he returned, then
you'll be rested from your works. I'm
still working. Last I checked,
>> read that commentary.
>> Those who lived according to the old
order of things,
>> they call it that the law and all that
stuff, the old order of things. Go
ahead.
>> Have come to a new hope, no longer
keeping the Sabbath, but the Lord's day
in which our life is blessed by him and
by his death.
>> That's good. So, this is where the idea
of the Lord's day comes from. Right now,
we're gonna read a little bit more
scripture, then we gonna get out of
here. Let's go to Isaiah. I think it's
Isaiah. Let me see.
>> Yeah,
we I'm I'm a wise person. Like, how how
did we get here? So, I like reading
stuff like that.
Let's go to uh Isaiah 24.
Isaiah 24.
And these people got all these people
around the world following this
nonsensical garbage.
>> Isaiah 24,
we start reading at verse 5. Isaiah
24:5. Go ahead.
>> The earth also is defiled under the
inhabitants thereof.
>> Because they have transgressed the laws,
changed the ordinances, broken the
everlasting covenant. He said the earth
is defiled because people have changed
the way that God instructed us to
operate.
>> Yeah.
>> Read verse six. Go ahead.
>> Therefore had the curse devoured the
earth.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And they that dwell therein are
desolate.
>> Therefore the inhabitants of the earth
are burned and few men left.
>> So they going to have to pay for this.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. Let's go to Jeremiah 16.
Now of the men that are left because he
said these men going to be burned
>> for changing the ordinances. The earth
is out of whack. It's out of course.
>> So we going to see of of those that are
left what they going to say when the
Lord start raining down this destruction
and this hellfire at the Lord's day. The
real Lord's day, not Sunday.
Jeremiah 16, we're going to read one
verse here. Verse 19. Jeremiah 16,
verse 19.
When you get it, go ahead. Oh Lord, my
strength and my fortress, my refuge in
the day of affliction.
>> The Gentiles shall come unto thee from
the ends of the earth.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And shall say, Surely our fathers have
inherited lies,
>> vanity, and things wherein there is no
profit.
>> At that day, they're going to be like,
"Dad,
>> we we messed up on that,
>> right? But it's going to be too late."
>> Yes.
So what we showed is that the Lord's day
is not Sunday. The Lord's day is this
day of destruction where the Lord comes
and takes his seat on the throne of
David to be established forever.
>> Amen.
>> We're going to read a little bit more
about the saints inheriting the kingdom.
Let's turn to Daniel chapter 7. And then
I got a warning for everybody that's
coming out of this book. It ain't coming
from me. I'm just reading it to you.
Daniel chapter 7
and we gonna start reading at verse
18 because it's going to be a glorious
day when the Lord comes and establish
his kingdom. But I'm trying to be right
beside him. Amen.
>> That jo should have been louder. Like I
>> Yeah,
>> man. Listen,
>> it ain't no other option.
>> Right.
>> Yeah. We still taking in all the all the
stuff that happen,
>> man. Don't get don't get messmerized by
the blood and smoke and all that other
stuff. Stay focused on the prize,
>> right? I'm just showing you what's
written.
>> Daniel chapter 7, pick up verse 18. Go
ahead.
>> But the saints of the most high
>> shall take the kingdom. Yeah.
>> And possess the kingdom forever, even
forever and ever. At that time, you
might see me running around the church
and doing back flips and kicking over
chairs and doing all that craziness,
>> right?
>> At that day,
>> yeah,
>> but ain't no reason to do it now,
>> right? I'm still in d. We all still in
danger right now.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Right. Skip down to verse uh 21 and
continue.
>> I beheld and the same horn made war with
the saints and prevail against them.
>> 22
>> until the ancients of days came
>> and judgment was given to the saints of
the most high.
>> Uhhuh. And the time came that the saints
possess the kingdom.
>> That the saints going to possess the
kingdom.
>> Right. Skip down to 25 and continue.
>> And he shall speak great words against
the most high.
>> Talking about that little horn. Go
ahead.
>> And shall weigh out the saints of the
most high
>> and take to change times and laws, and
they shall be given unto his into his
hand until a time and times and the
dividing of time.
>> Now that's the great tribulation. But
what did we show comes right after the
great tribulation, the day of the Lord,
>> keep reading 26.
>> But the judgment shall sit.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And they shall take away his dominion,
>> right?
>> To consume and to destroy it unto the
end.
>> Go ahead.
>> And the kingdom and the dominion and the
greatness of the kingdom under the whole
heaven
>> shall be given to the people of the
saints of the most high, whose kingdom
is an everlasting kingdom, and all
dominions shall serve and obey him.
>> Amen. go to uh Revelation chapter 20.
You got to think about this because the
way jurisdictions are set up now, you
know, we in Florida, they got their own
statutes and laws that they want us to
follow, but when the Lord return,
everybody on the earth is going to be
following the exact same law.
>> Yeah.
>> The exact same law.
>> It don't matter where you going to live
at, he going to be king over the whole
earth. We ain't going to have no
governors over Florida and and govern
over Ohio that got different ways of
doing things. It's going to be one way
of doing things.
>> Revelation 20.
Pick up verse 4. Revelation 20 verse 4.
When you get it, go ahead.
>> And I saw thrones
>> and they sat upon them and judgment was
given unto them. And I saw the souls of
them that were beheaded for the witness
of Jesus and for the word of God,
>> and which had not worshiped the beast,
neither his image, neither had received
his mark upon their forehead or in their
hands.
>> And they lived and reigned with Christ a
thousand years.
>> Right?
>> But the rest of the dead lived not again
until the thousand years were finished.
>> This is the first resurrection.
>> Amen. Go ahead.
>> Blessed and holy is he that had part in
the first resurrection. Anybody trying
to be in the first resurrection?
>> Yeah.
>> Listen,
man. Go ahead, bro.
>> And such the second death had no power,
>> but they shall be priests of God and of
Christ and shall reign with him a
thousand years.
>> So, this whole thing about the Lord's
day is setting up his establishment of
the of the saint of him taking the
kingship and the saints possessing the
kingdom which will be the earth.
>> Right.
>> I'm trying to be in that number.
>> Yeah. Right. Now, we got four more. We
going to skip down to second Peter
chapter 3. And the reason we go to this
is because
I got to put some warnings on the table
because again, you know, a lot of us
think sometimes because we come in here,
we keep the Sabbath days, keep the feast
days, and all that stuff. We scotfree.
We got to keep reading,
>> right?
>> Second Peter 3,
you ain't lying.
When you get a new body, you can rejoice
at that moment, not a moment sooner.
Second Peter 3, we're going to start
reading at verse 9 because, you know,
people talk about God's grace. People
talk about God's mercy. This is his
grace and this is his mercy.
>> Right. Uh second Peter 3, pick up verse
9 and continue.
>> The Lord is not slack concerning his
promise.
>> So that day is coming and he ain't
slacking. Go ahead. as some men count
slackness, but is longsuffering to us
work, not willing that any should
perish, but that all should come to
repentance.
>> The Lord don't want to kill anybody. You
can read that in multiple places. You
read in Ezekiel 18, you read in Ezekiel
the 33rd chapter. He doesn't want to
kill anybody. So, he's giving you time.
So, when he shows up, you going to be
without excuse, right? Keep reading.
Verse 10. But the day of the Lord will
come as a thief in the night,
>> in the which the heaven shall pass away
with a great noise,
>> and the elements shall melt with fervent
heat.
>> The earth also and the works that are
therein shall be burned up.
>> That's some hot heat. Go ahead.
>> Seeing then that all these things shall
be dissolved.
>> What manner of person ought ye to be in
all holy conversation
and godliness?
>> So I pose the same question. If we
didn't read all this stuff and we know
the Lord gonna bring all this
destruction. Yeah. How should you be
operating?
>> Right.
>> Go ahead. 12.
>> Looking for and hasting unto the coming
of the day of the Lord.
>> Yeah.
>> Wherein the heavens being on fire shall
be dissolved
>> and the elements shall melt with fervent
heat.
>> Go ahead.
>> Nevertheless, we according to his
promise look for new heavens and a new
earth wherein dwell it righteousness.
>> Because righteousness don't dwell on
this earth right now.
>> No. That's why I said when the Lord come
back and he set up his kingship, the
whole world is going to operate by the
same law and you going to be operating
in righteousness. That's not going on
right now.
>> Go ahead.
>> Wherefore, beloved, seeing that you look
for such things,
>> be diligent.
>> Yeah.
>> That you may be found of him in peace
without spot and blemish.
>> Blameless.
>> So you need to be without spot. You need
to be blameless.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. or you going to get caught up in
the hailstones and the blood and the
dead fish and all that. Yeah.
>> The bitter waters. I don't want to get
caught up in none of that.
>> Right.
>> Right. Let's go to uh 1 Thessalonians 5.
These are the last three. 1
Thessalonians 5.
And we're going to start reading at
verse
verse to 1 Thessalonians 5.
We're going to start reading at verse
two.
All these uh places we keep reading keep
telling you the day of the Lord is
coming. It's coming. It's coming. It's
coming. So, he's just telling you get
ready. All right.
1 Thessalonians 5, start reading at
verse two. Go ahead.
>> For you, for yourselves know perfectly
that the day of the Lord cometh, so
cometh as a thief in the night.
>> Peter just said the same thing. is
coming like a thief, right? Especially
for those that don't know. Verse three,
>> for when they shall say peace and
safety,
>> then sudden destruction cometh upon them
>> as travail upon a woman with child,
>> and they shall not escape.
>> Ain't nobody escaping that. Go ahead.
>> But ye, brethren,
>> are not in darkness,
>> that that day should overtake you as a
thief.
>> And that's the whole point of coming in
here and getting this lesson because we
know this thing is coming.
>> Yeah.
>> So it ain't going to overtake us because
we know what's going on. Mhm.
>> That don't mean there ain't going to be
a fearful time and a scary time, but at
least we know what's going on
>> because the people that are not
expecting this when this thing come.
Yeah.
>> And like, what in the world is going on
right now?
>> Read verse five. Go ahead.
>> Ye are all the children of light.
>> Yeah.
>> And the children of the day.
>> Yes, sir.
>> We are not of the night,
>> nor of darkness.
>> Go ahead.
>> Therefore, let us not sleep as do
others, but let us watch and be sober.
You know how people would be saying
stuff like uh you know they just waiting
for God and all this stuff. I'd be like,
"Man, the Lord told us to keep watch."
>> I'd be asking people, "Do you know what
we supposed to keep watch for?"
>> You keeping watch. That means that
there's something that's coming that's
going to give me a signal that something
about to happen. Yeah.
>> But what if you don't know what to keep
watch for?
>> Right.
>> Right. It's going to come on you like a
thief in the night.
>> Let's go to Matthew 24.
If you go into uh 2 Thessalonians 2,
Paul tells you that that day of the Lord
is not going to come except there come a
great falling away first.
>> Right? So we got to stay diligent. We
got to stay ready
in Jesus name.
We got to stay ready. So what we going
to read about here is a brother
for half a second lost sight. He missed
the mark. Matthew 24, we're going to
start reading at verse 42. When you get
it, go ahead and start reading.
>> Watch therefore,
>> for you know not what hour your Lord do
come.
>> That's for all of us. Watch because we
don't know what hour he's going to come.
Go ahead.
>> But know this, that if the good man of
the house had known in what watch the
thief would come,
>> Uhhuh. He would have he he would have
watched and would not have suffered his
house to be broken broken up.
>> That's right. If you was up at, you
know, 2:52 a.m. when you knew the thief
was going to come, you can get on your
microphone. Hey, go ahead, chief. I'm
already waiting for you, man. Just go
ahead and turn on around.
>> Right. That's how it's
But what I'm saying, he he trying to
give you an example. If you know what to
keep watch for,
>> then when this thing come, it ain't
gonna come on you unawares and you gonna
know what's going on. Read 44.
Therefore, be you also ready,
>> for in such an hour as you think not,
the son of man cometh.
>> Go ahead.
>> Who then is a faithful and wise servant,
>> whom his lord had made ruler over his
household?
>> Uhhuh.
>> To give them meat in due season.
>> Go ahead.
>> Blessed is that servant whom his lord
when he cometh shall find him so doing.
>> So you know you started off doing good.
The Lord said, man, you know I put you
over my goods. Right. Go ahead. Verily I
say unto you that he shall make him
ruler over all his goods.
>> So it says that if he continue that when
the Lord returns, he going to find him
doing well. He should be okay.
But verse 48,
>> but and if that evil servant shall say
in his heart, my lord delayeth his
coming.
>> Now that's your warning. That's for all
of us. We get that short moment where we
say, "Man, the Lord ain't coming today."
>> Yeah. You know, it's a stupid spirit
that come in your mind and you say
something like, "Oh, the the Lord will
forgive me for this one."
>> Right. That one half second slip could
cost you your eternal salvation.
>> Yeah.
>> Half a second to doing something stupid,
>> right? Because something came into your
mind to convince you that it was okay to
do.
>> Yeah.
>> So, it says, "But and if that evil
servant shall say in his heart, my lord
delayeth his coming." Go ahead.
>> And shall begin to smite his fellow
servants,
>> Uhhuh. Uh-huh.
>> And to eat and drink with drunkenness.
>> Go ahead. With a drunken.
>> With a drunken.
>> Uhhuh.
>> The Lord of that servant shall come in a
day when he lookth not for him.
>> And in an hour that he is not aware of.
>> And shall cut him a thunder and appoint
him his portion with the hypocrites.
They shall be weeping and nashing of
teeth.
>> If y'all don't know, that's the lake of
fire. You go to Isaiah the 33rd chapter
and he tell you what's going to happen
to the hypocrites. He said when they
wake up after the resurrection, he said
they're going to be facing the king of
terrorists.
>> Right. Let's go to the last place. Let's
go to Luke
21.
Luke 21.
So even though we understand what the
Lord's day is, that don't mean that we
can be slack,
>> right?
more. So, we should be vigilant in our
conversation and how we operate,
right? Luke 21, we're going to start
reading at verse 34. When you get it, go
ahead.
>> And take heed to yourselves,
>> least at any time your heart be
overcharged with sufficing and
drunkenness, and the cares of this life.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And so that that day come upon un upon
you unawares.
>> That day come upon you unaware. So he
said, "Take heed to yourself because the
cares of anybody try to, you know, when
the cares of this life come, they always
take priority.
>> We got to put God first, right? We got
to put his kingdom first because you can
put the cares of this life first and you
can slip up on your journey,
>> right? Go ahead. 35.
>> For as a snare shall come on all them
that dwell on the face of the whole
earth."
>> Go ahead.
>> Watch ye therefore.
>> Keep We read that about four times in a
row.
>> He told you about the day of the Lord
and he Keep saying, "Keep watch."
>> Go ahead.
>> Watch ye therefore
>> and pray always
>> that you may be accounted worthy to
escape all these things that shall come
to pass and to stand before the son of
man.
>> Because you better believe these things
going to come to pass.
>> Yeah.
>> At that day, I pray y'all got some
understanding in Jesus name.
Father.